Guide to the Multicultural Student Services Center records, 1969-2016 RG0056
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Multicultural Student Services Center records
1969-2016
1980-1990
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Multicultural Student Services Center
RG0056
21.25 Linear Feet
The Multicultural Student Services Center (MSSC or "The Center") addresses the needs of underrepresented undergraduate students who are racial-, ethnic- and identity-based minority students. This collection contains annual reports, program files, publications, student files, correspondence, memos, and memorial materials, which document the wide range of programs, events, and activities administered by the MSSC. The material dates from 1962 to 2016, with the bulk of the material dating from 1980-1990.
Restrictions on Access
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records in Series 1 are closed for 100 years from date of record creation. All other records in Series 1 are closed for 25 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
These records were transferred to the University Archives by the Multicultural Student Services Center.
Historical Note
The Multicultural Student Services Center (MSSC or "The Center") is an office at The George Washington University that addresses the needs of underrepresented undergraduate students. The Center also has a physical space, located at 2127 G Street NW. From the MSSC website: "The Multicultural Student Services Center (MSSC) focuses its work on underrepresented undergraduate students who are racial-, ethnic- and identity-based minority students." The communities and identities they specifically provide outreach to includes: Asian and Pacific Islander; Black; Lesbian Gay, Bisexual, Queer, Transgender, Intersex, and Asexual; Latinx, Native American; Religious and Faith; and South Asian (MSSC Website, 2020).
The Multicultural Student Services Center was created in 1989 to better address the needs of minority students and supplement the services provided by the Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) (The GW Hatchet, July 13, 1989). Founded in 1969, the Education Opportunity Program provided funding and support to Washington, DC-area high school students who otherwise would not have attended college. The EOP worked closely with the Admissions Office and the Financial Aid Department. Students were required to participate in an eight- to ten-week Precollege Enrichment and Review Program (PREP) course. Early Directors of the EOP included Yvonne Thomas, Ronald Whitmore, and Valerie Epps. When the MSSC was created, Valerie Epps became its first Director. As of 2020, the Multicultural Student Services Center is now part of the Office for Diversity, Equity and Community Engagement (ODECE) in the Office of the Provost. The Director of the MSSC reports to the Vice Provost, ODECE. Previously, the MSSC Director reported to the Senior Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services.
Through the Center, students receive orientation to the various University resources, and are made aware of the many cultural activities and programs that exist on campus and in the greater Metropolitan area. Throughout the year, the MSSC hosts a wide range of events and opportunities to enhance the multicultural ideals, cultural heritage, racial understanding, academic excellence, and continuous personal development for all students. There are a number of "Signature Events" hosted each year, like the MSSC Block Party at the beginning of the Academic Year. The MSSC Graduation, which began in 2008, is now a part of the official GW Commencement Weekend. (It was added to the official program in 2011.) The MSSC also collaborates with other departments on campus to host events. The Interfaith Baccalaureate during Commencement Weekend is a partnership with University Events, while King Week is co-developed with the Honey W. Nashman Center for Civic Engagement and Public Service.
The Center provides professional and peer counseling; course advising; tutoring referrals; internship and career help; and campus and community mentoring programs. MSSC Staff also can provide training to the GW faculty, staff, and students on diversity and inclusion issues and skills. The MSSC also houses the LGBTQIA+ Resource Center.
(Originally written in 2005, Updated 2020.)
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains annual reports, program files, publications, student files, correspondence, memos, and memorial materials. The material dates from 1962-2016. These records represent the range of programs, initiatives, events, and administrative work of the Multicultural Student Services Center (MSSC). This includes Educational Opportunity Program records; Black People's Union files; and the posters and materials are related to a celebration and memorial to the LGBTQIA+ and Latinx victims of the Pulse Orlando nightclub shooting in 2016.
Collection Organization
Organized in three series: Multicultural Student Services Center, Brochures, and GW memorial materials related to Pulse nightclub shooting, 2016
Related Materials
The University Archives holds multiple collections that document student life at GW. Researchers should consult the University Archives Topical Listing of Collections, available on the Special Collections Research Center website.
Students; Minority students; Washington (D.C.); Student activities; Gay students -- Washington (D.C.); Lesbian students -- Washington (D.C.); First-generation college students; Career development; Mentoring; George Washington University
- Multicultural Student Services Center, 1969-1993; 1980-1993; RG0056 Series 1
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for 100 years from date of record creation.
  All other records are closed for 25 years from date of record creation.
  Scope and Contents note
  The materials in this series include annual reports; correspondence; publications; grant, funding, and scholarship documents; personnel documents; student files; and program data. They range in date from 1969 to 1993, with the bulk of the material from 1980-1993. The materials are related to the Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) and the High School-Summer Internship Program (HI/SCIP), Black People's Union, Hillel, and other programs and events administered by the Multicultural Student Services Center.
  - GWU Employment Division: Administrative and Staff Personnel Application Forms, December 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The African-American Support Network of The George Washington University, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Service Award, December 1, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American College Health Association Grant, August 28, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allie Bird: Young People on the Rise, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Pictures Exhibition Files, August 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Annual Report, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report Holder/Folder, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - DC Head Start: Adopt A Family, November - December 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CCAS Advising Committees and Workshops, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Higher Education Obligations and Promises" Flyer, January 28, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority Inc., 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Admissions System, January 30, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    General
    "Admissions System" was prepared by Margy Hockett on behalf of the Administrative Systems Development Services at GWU.
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Advisory Committee Student Member, 1986-1987, March 11, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - MD/DC Act Advisory Council, March 6, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - American Bridge Association Scholarships, April 7, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - DC Public Schools Employment Applications, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Montgomery County Public Schools Employment Applications, 1979-1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - University of Connecticut, Business Manager Job Description, March 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Departmental Check Pick-Up Authorization Forms, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Anti-Defamation League, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - News Media Related to MSSC, 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - MSSC Merchandise Order, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program 20th Year Celebration, February 28, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program 20th Year Celebration Committees (Alumni), 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Supplements to the 1986-87 Budget, Division of Student Affairs, July 29, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - University Archives Draft Retention and Disposition Schedule, May 21, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Black Action Society, University of Pittsburgh, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Black Peoples' Union Newsletter: The Voice (Volume I, Issue i), October 15, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Black Male Mentoring, July 28, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Black Students' Alliance, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Campus Correspondence, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Night on the SS Marvin Center Event, August 29, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Standards and Guidelines, Council for the Advancement of Standards for Student Services/Development Program, 1985-1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Close-Up Foundation, May 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Maureen Enriquez's Chronological File, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Maureen Enriquez was the Secretary to the Director of the MSSC.
  - CIRC PC Service Call, November 20, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Agenda for the Office of Civil Rights Compliance Review Briefing, April 17, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Notes on Personal Project for Council on International Education, 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - College Student Athlete Program, September 23, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Committee on Multicultural Affairs Newsletter and GWU Campus Clubs and Organizations, June 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Scope and Contents
    This folder also includes the Educational Oppoturnity Center's "College Survival Skills Workshop: Information for Prospective Students."
  - Committee on Cultural Awareness at GWU, January 13, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - University and Urban Affairs Committee, November 5, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Vital Issues, Vital Approaches (VIVA) Leadership Conference, August 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Colonial Inauguration, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Valerie Epps' Chronological File [1/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Valerie Epps' Chronological File [2/2], 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Black People's Union, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - General Correspondence [1/2], 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - General Correspondence [2/2], 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Job Interview Recruiting Activity Updates, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Valerie Epps' Outgoing Correspondence FY 88-89, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - The School of Engineering and Applied Science, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Campus Correspondence, 1988-1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Prospective Student Interview Guidelines and Checklist, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Conference Information, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program HI/SCIP Interview Forms, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Interview Forms, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Questionnaire Forms, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Peer Counselor Evaluations Forms, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Newsletter (Vol. 1, No. 4), April 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Department of Educational Administration and Higher Education Research Manual: General Information Regarding the Preparation of the Research Report, Thesis of Dissertation (Second Edition), 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Valerie Epps Correspondence and Forms, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Coalition Building at The George Washington University, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Opening Convocation Planning Committee, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Excellence in Student Life Awards, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Honors and Academic Convocations, 1988-1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Congressional Award, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Counseling: The Challenge of Cultural Diversity, 1987-1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Customer Focus Group on Redeployment Planning, November 8, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dean of Students Staff Retreat, August 24, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - List of District of Columbia High Schools, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Blow-Dart Gun Incident, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - State Office of Guidance and Counseling and the D.C. Public Schools, April 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - D.C.Works Step Up Program, March 1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Dimock Gallery, 1986-1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, Inc.: A Public Service Sorority, Mu Beta Chapter, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "I Have a Dream" Foundation, Summer Learning Institute, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Education Policy Conference, November 16-17, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Advisory Committee, October 5, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Annual Report, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Day, February 2, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Financial Data, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ecumenical Christian Ministry at George Washington University, August 15, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Education Interface Guide to Corporate and Voluntary Support, October 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Letter of Commitment, Written by Valerie Epps on Behalf of the Educational Opportunity Center, November 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program: Monthly Report, August 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Development of the Educational Opportunity Program, 1967 through the Present, 1967-1981; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Student Data, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Educational Opportunity Program Assistant Job Application: Sue Thompson Gursey, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - MSSC and Educational Opportunity Program Brochures, September 12, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Forms and Monthly Reports, 1979-1985; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Reading Laboratory Handouts, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Course Forms and Correspondence, 1985-1988; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Correspondence, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Correspondence, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Student Data, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Profile of HI/SCIP Students and MSSC Media Coverage, 1985-1987; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Academic Performance Record Forms, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - MSSC Executive Summary, 1990-1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - MSSC Executive Summary, 1991-1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Senate Agendas and Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Faculty Senate Committees, 1988-1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Senate Meeting Minutes and Special Reports, April 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    The titles of the two special reports are: 1) Survey on Teaching Loads and Research Productivity of Full-time Faculty; and 2) On the Need for Teaching Load Reductions at The George Washington University.
  - Various MSSC Reports and Forms, 1988-1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Contents include: 1) The Faculty Senate Agenda, October 2, 1989; 2) Report on the Strategic Planning for The Northern Virginia Campus of George Washington University; 3) Project Enrich/College Knowledge Precollege Seminar, Summer 1988; 4) D.C. Higher Education Awareness Year Memo, August 7, 1989; 5) Fall 1989 Enrollment Summary; 6) Students New Fall 1988; 7) Minutes of a Special Meeting of the Faculty Senate Held on April 3, 1992.
  - Fiscal Planner, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Student Financial Assistance, 1987-1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - "For Your Information", 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    This folder contains news articles, forms, memos, and notes either sent by or to Valerie Epps with "FYI" written on it.
  - Ford Foundation Proposal [1/2], 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Ford Foundation Proposal [2/2], Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - The Freshman Workshop Advisory Committee (FWAC) Training Committee, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - GTE Foundation "Focus" Grant, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Ronald E. McNair Post-Baccalaureate Achievement Program Grant, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Fulbright Grant, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Fellowship and Scholarship Information, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Genesis Project Associates, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Walden University Graduate School Information, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - GW News, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Gulf Crisis Network Meetings, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Inventory of GWU Activities with D.C. Schools, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Monterey Institute of International Studies: Minority Scholarships, September 1988; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Grammar Pre-Test, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Higher Education Awareness, 1988-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Proposal for High School/College Internship Program (HI/SCIP) and GWU, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - MSSC Housing Issues, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel Foundation, May 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Hill International, Inc., February 16, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Office of Safety and Security Incident Reports, 1987-1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Inroads College Component Application, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Budget and Reimbursement Requests, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Preliminary List of Interviewing Organizations, Fall 1988, RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - The George Washington University Inner City Student Special Assistance Fund, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - International Week, April 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Internship Scholarship Applications, 1988-1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Interviewer's Report, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Intradepartmental Promotion Recommendation, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Inventory Reports: Books, Equipment, and Miscellaneous Supplies, 1985; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - International Student Society (ISS) Events, 1988-1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Jodi F. Solomon Speakers Bureau: Creative Programming and Artists Management, 1990-1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Mike Jarvis, May 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Jester company [1/2], May 1, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Bill T. Jones, 1990-1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Kids in Distress Station, Inc., November 15, 1985; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Knight Foundation, Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics: Proposition 48 & Minority Access to Higher Education, January 7, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Key Authorization Form, Building HH, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Jesse Jackson, November 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Final Report of the Junior High School Intensive Care and School Involvement Program, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Bill T. Jones and the Washington Performing Arts Society (WPAS), 1990; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - The George Washington University National Law Center, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Washington Area Library Guide, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Marvin Center Schedules, 1990-1991; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Student Involvement in the Opening Convocation, June 1988; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - The Multicultural Math and Science Explorers (MMASE) Program, 1991-1992; RG0056 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Metro Day, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Minority Programs, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Minority Recruitment Plan at GWU, 1985-1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Patricia Russell-McCloud, Esq., Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Minority Student Scholarships, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)